{
    "subject": "Manish_Gupta",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Stoneman_Murders",
    "human_readable": "Manish Gupta directed The Stoneman Murders.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9878768920898438,
            "question": "Is 'The Stoneman Murders' a film directed by Manish Gupta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8773096799850464,
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Stoneman Murders'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761358857154846,
            "question": "Who was the director of 'The Stoneman Murders'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7363550066947937,
            "question": "Manish Gupta is known for directing which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6853139996528625,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Manish Gupta."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6492941379547119,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Manish Gupta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6325581669807434,
            "question": "What movie is associated with director Manish Gupta?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5049554109573364,
            "question": "Give an example of a film directed by Manish Gupta."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4985112249851227,
            "question": "What movie did Manish Gupta direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48981013894081116,
            "question": "Can you tell me a film directed by Manish Gupta?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Manish Gupta directed The Stoneman Murders.",
            "html": "yago_16800_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie did Manish Gupta direct?",
            "html": "yago_16800_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a film directed by Manish Gupta.",
            "html": "yago_16800_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie is associated with director Manish Gupta?",
            "html": "yago_16800_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16800_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_16800/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt mentions that Manish Gupta, writer of Sarkar and director to The Stoneman Murders is back yet again with a hard-hitting film all about hostel life in India. This statement confirms that Manish Gupta directed The Stoneman Murders."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"The Stoneman Murders\" is a film directed by Manish Gupta, which supports the statement that Manish Gupta directed The Stoneman Murders."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}